Guide to the Dwight Hall, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1911-1980; Accession 1988-A-105
  - Old Library, 1931 (Box 168, Folder 4659 - 4660)
  - Dedication of New Dwight Hall Office in the Old Library, 1931 (Box 168, Folder 4661)
  - 50th Anniversary Material, 1937 (Box 168, Folder 4662)
  - 75th Anniversary, 1956 (Box 168, Folder 4663)
  - Yale Corporation: Concerning Jurisdiction over Dwight Hall, 1883-1931 (Box 168, Folder 4664)
  - Correspondence Concerning Jurisdiction over Dwight Hall, 1974-1980 (Box 168, Folder 4665)
  - Yale University Christian Association, 1919-1920 (Box 169, Folder 4666)
  - Conferences at Yale, 1939 (Box 169, Folder 4667)
  - Divinity School Pamphlets, 1926-1944 (Box 169, Folder 4668)
  - Discussion Groups, 1950's (Box 169, Folder 4669)
  - Dwight Hall Information
    - 1930's (Box 169, Folder 4670)
    - 1940's (Box 169, Folder 4671)
    - 1950's (Box 169, Folder 4672)
    - 1960's (Box 169, Folder 4673)
    - 1970's (Box 169, Folder 4674)
  - Labor Pamphlets, 1918-1919 (Box 169, Folder 4675)
  - Memorabilia, 1915 (Box 169, Folder 4676)
  - Ordinations at Yale, 1940's (Box 170, Folder 4677)
  - Religion/Christianity at Yale, 1930's (Box 170, Folder 4678)
  - R.O.T.C. at Yale, 1918 (Box 170, Folder 4679)
  - Yale War Memorial, circa 1921 (Box 170, Folder 4680)
  - Wartime Yale, 1940's (Box 170, Folder 4681)
  - University Pamphlets, 1910's (Box 170, Folder 4682)
  - Yale-in-China Pamphlets, 1910's (Box 170, Folder 4683)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1920's (Box 170, Folder 4684)
  - Africa, 1930 (Box 170, Folder 4685)
  - Alderman, Board of, 1973-1974 (Box 170, Folder 4686)
  - American Association of Theological Schools, 1958 (Box 170, Folder 4687)
  - Bible Study, 1913-1915 (Box 170, Folder 4688)
  - Boarding Houses, 1925 (Box 171, Folder 4689)
  - Borden, William Whiting, Pamphlets on Founder of the Yale Hope Mission, post 1913 (Box 171, Folder 4690)
  - Work With Boys, 1914 (Box 171, Folder 4691)
  - China, 1915 (Box 171, Folder 4692)
  - The Church Society for College Work, undated (Box 171, Folder 4693)
  - Committee on Friendly Relations among Foreign Students, 1928-1929 (Box 171, Folder 4694)
  - Conferences, 1910's-1960's (Box 171, Folder 4695)
  - Dixwell Group, 1940's (Box 171, Folder 4696)
  - Drugs and Alcohol, 1972 (Box 171, Folder 4697)
  - Education, 1928-1960's (Box 171, Folder 4698)
  - The Episcopal Church, circa 1942 (Box 171, Folder 4699)
  - The Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1935-1936 (Box 171, Folder 4700)
  - French Relief, 1916 (Box 171, Folder 4701)
  - Grenfell Mission, 1919 (Box 171, Folder 4702)
  - Health Pamphlets, 1917 (Box 171, Folder 4703)
  - Hospitals, 1912-1913 (Box 171, Folder 4704)
  - International Student Service, 1934-1935 (Box 171, Folder 4705)
  - Inter-Racial Commission, 1947-1949 (Box 171, Folder 4706)
  - The Inter-Varsity Christian Fellowship, post 1939 (Box 171, Folder 4707)
  - Japan: Pamphlets, 1915 (Box 171, Folder 4708)
  - Japanese-Americans, 1940's (Box 171, Folder 4709)
  - Labor Pamphlets, 1930 (Box 172, Folder 4710)
  - League of Evangelical Students, undated (Box 172, Folder 4711)
  - Lists and Guides, 1914-1916 (Box 172, Folder 4712)
  - Missions, 1910's (Box 172, Folder 4713)
  - Moving Pictures, 1945-1946 (Box 172, Folder 4714 - 4715)
  - National Center for Voluntary Action, circa 1970's (Box 172, Folder 4716)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1938 (Box 172, Folder 4717)
  - National Council on Religion in Higher Education, 1944 (Box 172, Folder 4718)
  - National Intercollegiate Christian Council, 1931-1932 (Box 172, Folder 4719)
  - National Policy Reports, 1944 (Box 172, Folder 4720)
  - New Haven, 1916 (Box 172, Folder 4721)
  - New Haven Maps, undated (Box 173, Folder 4722)
  - North American Student Movements, 1914-1915 (Box 173, Folder 4723)
  - Ordination Programs, 1929 (Box 173, Folder 4724)
  - The Patriot Party Posters, circa 1970 (Box 173, Folder 4725)
  - Peace / Disarmament, 1925 (Box 173, Folder 4726)
  - Peace Corps, circa 1970's (Box 173, Folder 4727)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission, 1972-1976 (Box 173, Folder 4728)
  - Planned Parenthood of Connecticut, 1955 (Box 173, Folder 4729)
  - Prayer Pamphlets, 1920's (Box 173, Folder 4730)
  - Presbyterians, 1935 (Box 173, Folder 4731)
  - Prison Leaflets, 1916-1918 (Box 173, Folder 4732)
  - Programs: Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 173, Folder 4733)
  - Psychology, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 4734)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1945 (Box 173, Folder 4735)
  - Reports: Miscellaneous, 1920's (Box 173, Folder 4736)
  - Socialist Party, circa 1960's (Box 173, Folder 4737)
  - The Southernaires' Hymns for Male Quartet, 1943 (Box 174, Folder 4738)
  - Speech Reprints, 1940's (Box 174, Folder 4739)
  - Student Friendship Fund, 1921-1922 (Box 174, Folder 4740)
  - Student Volunteer Movement, 1931-1932 (Box 174, Folder 4741)
  - Summer Programs / Work Camps, 1915 (Box 174, Folder 4742)
  - Summer Retreats, 1936 (Box 174, Folder 4743)
  - Turkey, 1952-1953 (Box 174, Folder 4744)
  - U.S.O., 1943 (Box 174, Folder 4745)
  - Unitarianism, 1950's (Box 174, Folder 4746)
  - VISTA (Volunteers in Service to America), circa 1970's (Box 174, Folder 4747)
  - World Student Christian Federation, 1938-1941 (Box 174, Folder 4748)
  - World Student Service Fund, 1946-1947 (Box 174, Folder 4749)
  - World War I Pamphlets, circa 1917-1919 (Box 174, Folder 4750)
  - World War II Pamphlets, 1940's (Box 174, Folder 4751)
  - YMCA of Connecticut, 1929 (Box 174, Folder 4752)
  - Constitution / By-Laws, 1936 (Box 174, Folder 4753)
  - International Committee of YMCAs, circa 1916 (Box 174, Folder 4754)
  - YMCA: Manuals for Leaders, 1945 (Box 174, Folder 4755)
  - YMCA: Manuals for Leaders, 1946 (Box 174, Folder 4756)
  - National Council of the YMCA, 1944 (Box 175, Folder 4757)
  - National Student Christian Movement (YMCA), post 1929 (Box 175, Folder 4758)
  - New England Christian Movements / Associations (YMCA), 1916 (Box 175, Folder 4759)
  - Wiley Commission: YMCA, 1943-1944 (Box 175, Folder 4760)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1916-1977 (Box 175, Folder 4761 - 4763)
  - Deputations
    - First Congregational Church in Ansonia, CT, 1939-1943 (Box 176, Folder 4764)
    - Bergen County YMCA, 1919-1920 (Box 176, Folder 4765)
    - Bridgeport YMCA, 1912-1916 (Box 176, Folder 4766)
    - Bridgeport YMCA, 1919 (Box 176, Folder 4767)
    - First Congregational Church in Bristol, CT, 1937-1940 (Box 176, Folder 4768)
    - Bronxville, NY, 1933-1944 (Box 176, Folder 4769)
    - Center Mouches, NY, 1937-1941 (Box 176, Folder 4770)
    - Chester, CT, 1939-1941 (Box 176, Folder 4771)
    - First Church of Christ in Clinton, CT, 1940-1943 (Box 176, Folder 4772)
    - Derby and Shelton YMCA, 1912-1916 (Box 176, Folder 4773)
    - First Congregational Church in Derby, CT, 1937-1940 (Box 176, Folder 4774)
    - Dobbs Ferry, 1942 (Box 176, Folder 4775)
    - East Haven, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 4776)
    - East Lynn, MA, 1935 (Box 176, Folder 4777)
    - Fairfield County YMCA, 1918-1920 (Box 176, Folder 4778 - 4779)
    - Florence, 1943 (Box 176, Folder 4780)
    - Haddam, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 4781)
    - Hartford YMCA, 1919-1920 (Box 176, Folder 4782)
    - Hartford, 1936 (Box 176, Folder 4783)
    - Haydenville, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 4784)
    - Holyoke, undated (Box 176, Folder 4785)
    - Litchfield County YMCA, 1919-1920 (Box 176, Folder 4786)
    - Madison, 1946 (Box 176, Folder 4787)
    - Mansfield Center, 1941 (Box 176, Folder 4788)
    - Middlebury, 1941-1942 (Box 176, Folder 4789)
    - New Canaan, CT, 1919 (Box 176, Folder 4790)
    - New York: Beck Memorial Church, 1934-1935 (Box 176, Folder 4791)
    - North Arlington, 1941 (Box 176, Folder 4792)
    - Northfield, 1918-1920 (Box 176, Folder 4793)
    - Plainfield, 1946 (Box 176, Folder 4794)
    - Port Chester, NY, 1934-1935 (Box 176, Folder 4795)
    - Redding, CT, 1932 (Box 176, Folder 4796)
    - Seymour, CT, 1935 (Box 176, Folder 4797)
    - Simsbury, 1937-1941 (Box 176, Folder 4798)
    - Southampton, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 4799)
    - Southbury, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 4800)
    - Stamford, 1941 (Box 176, Folder 4801)
    - Stepney, 1937 (Box 176, Folder 4802)
    - Storrs, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 4803)
    - Taftville, 1941 (Box 176, Folder 4804)
    - Thompsonville, 1955-1956 (Box 176, Folder 4805)
    - Trumbull, 1941 (Box 176, Folder 4806)
    - Washington, 1946 (Box 176, Folder 4807)
    - Waterbury, 1942 (Box 176, Folder 4808)
    - Westhampton, 1941 (Box 176, Folder 4809)
    - White Plains, 1942 (Box 176, Folder 4810)
    - Williamsburg, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 4811)
    - Willimantic, CT, 1919 (Box 176, Folder 4812)
    - Wilton, CT, 1918-1919 (Box 176, Folder 4813)
    - Windsor, 1946 (Box 177, Folder 4814)
    - Woodmont Union Chapel, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 4815)
    - Worcester, 1913-1914 (Box 177, Folder 4816)
    - Yonkers, NY, 1946 (Box 177, Folder 4817)
  - Deputations: Churches
    - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 177, Folder 4818)
    - General, 1919 (Box 177, Folder 4819)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 177, Folder 4820)
    - Local (CT YMCAs and NY), 1919-1920 (Box 177, Folder 4821)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 177, Folder 4822)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 177, Folder 4823)
    - Letters, 1933-1934 (Box 177, Folder 4824)
    - James, 1934-1935 (Box 177, Folder 4825)
    - Letters Sent Out, 1935-1936 (Box 177, Folder 4826)
    - 1943 (Box 177, Folder 4827)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 177, Folder 4828)
    - Church Lists, undated (Box 177, Folder 4829)
  - Deputations: Preparatory Schools, Colleges
    - Briarcliff Junior College, 1948 (Box 177, Folder 4830)
    - Brown University Christian Association, 1913 (Box 177, Folder 4831)
    - Cheshire School, 1913-1914 (Box 177, Folder 4832)
    - Choate School, 1912-1915 (Box 177, Folder 4833)
    - Cushing Academy, 1912-1915 (Box 177, Folder 4834)
    - Groton School, 1915-1916 (Box 177, Folder 4835)
    - Guilford, CT, 1918-1919 (Box 177, Folder 4836)
    - Gunnery School, 1915-1916 (Box 177, Folder 4837)
    - Hotchkiss school, 1914-1916 (Box 177, Folder 4838)
    - The Hill School, 1919-1920 (Box 177, Folder 4839)
    - Kent School, 1914-1915 (Box 177, Folder 4840)
    - MacKenzie School, 1913 (Box 177, Folder 4841)
    - Mercersburg Academy, 1913-1916 (Box 177, Folder 4842)
    - Monson Academy, 1912 (Box 177, Folder 4843)
    - Montclair Academy, 1912-1916 (Box 177, Folder 4844)
    - Pawling School, 1914-1915 (Box 177, Folder 4845)
    - Peekskill Military Academy, 1913-1916 (Box 177, Folder 4846)
    - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1912-1916 (Box 177, Folder 4847)
    - Phillips Academy (Andover, MA), 1918 (Box 177, Folder 4848)
    - Powder Point School, 1915 (Box 177, Folder 4849)
    - Saint George's School, 1912-1914 (Box 177, Folder 4850)
    - Suffield School, 1920-1921 (Box 177, Folder 4851)
    - Taft School, 1937-1938 (Box 177, Folder 4852)
    - U.S. Military Academy at West Point, 1920 (Box 177, Folder 4853)
    - Westminster School, 1913-1919 (Box 177, Folder 4854)
  - Deputations: Schools in General
    - 1910-1913 (Box 177, Folder 4855)
    - Secondary Schools, 1910-1918 (Box 177, Folder 4856)
    - Mallory, Charles H., 1911-1916 (Box 177, Folder 4857)
    - Noyes, Morgan, 1913-1914 (Box 177, Folder 4858)
    - Preparatory Schools, 1917-1920 (Box 177, Folder 4859)
  - Deputation Correspondence
    - General Information, 1934 (Box 177, Folder 4860)
    - Letters Received, 1935-1936 (Box 177, Folder 4861)
    - General, 1936-1937 (Box 177, Folder 4862)
    - Ideas, 1944-1950 (Box 177, Folder 4863)
    - 1950-1954 (Box 177, Folder 4864)
  - "Ahearn's Press Release", 1970 (Box 178, Folder 4865)
  - Herbert Cahoon Magnetic Tapes, undated
  - Dwight Hall Magnetic Tape, circa 1970 (Box 178, Folder 4866)
  - "The Odds Were Against Us", circa 1970 (Box 179, Folder 4867)
  - Recording Disks, 1942 (Box 179, Folder 4868)
  - Dr. Richards, undated (Box 179, Folder 4869 - 4870)
  - "Wednesday Worship Discussion", circa 1970 (Box 179, Folder 4871)
  - "Word Rock" John Boyles Copy, circa 1970 (Box 179, Folder 4872)
  - Unidentified Magnetic Tapes, circa 1970
  - Eifler, Carl N., 1971-1973 (Box 180, Folder 4873)
  - Endowments
    - Acknowledgments and Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 180, Folder 4874)
    - Correspondence, Pledges: A. B. Clark, 1963 (Box 180, Folder 4875)
    - Drive, 1963 (Box 180, Folder 4876)
    - Fund, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 180, Folder 4877)
    - Records, 1962-1963 (Box 180, Folder 4878)
  - Freeman, Henry B., 1974-1975 (Box 180, Folder 4879)
  - Jeffers, Thomas L., 1970-1972 (Box 180, Folder 4880)
  - Montejano, David, 1971-1973 (Box 180, Folder 4881)
  - Perlman, Davis, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 4882)
  - Poindexter, Jim, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 4883)
  - Recommendations
    - 1940 (Box 180, Folder 4884)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 180, Folder 4885)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 4886)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 180, Folder 4887)
    - 1959 (Box 180, Folder 4888)
  - Schmidt, H. J.: Alternate Service Program, 1971-1973 (Box 180, Folder 4889)
  - Student Grades, 1936-1978 (Box 180, Folder 4890)
  - Unsworth, Bruce: I-O Classification, circa 1971 (Box 180, Folder 4891)
- Scrapbooks and minutes of council and committee meetings and correspondence, circa 1903-1980; Accession 1995-A-024
  - Scrapbooks
    - Dwight Hall, 1917-1922 (Box 1)
    - Yale Cosmopolitan Club, 1927 (Box 2)
    - Dwight Hall
      - 1921-1926 (Box 2)
      - 1926-1957 (Box 2)
      - 1929-1933 (Box 2)
      - 1929-1948 (Box 3)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 3)
      - 1940, 1947 (Box 3)
      - 1933-1938 (Box 4)
      - 1938-1942 (Box 4)
      - 1941-1947 (Box 5)
      - 1948-1949 (Box 5)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 6)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 6)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 6)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 7)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 7)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 7)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 7)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 7)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 7)
    - Yale Charities Drive
      - 1942-1943 (Box 8)
      - 1946 (Box 8)
      - 1951 (Box 8)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 9)
  - Minutes
    - University Council of Yale, 1903-1906 (Box 10)
    - University Christian Association (YUCA) (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee
      - 1925-1934 (Box 10)
      - 1944 (Box 10)
    - Staff Council, 1951 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee [includes YUCA correspondence and other related Dwight Hall groups' information], 1952 (Box 10)
    - Yale Hope Mission, 1965-1977 (Box 10)
    - Yale Cosmopolitan Club
      - 1908-1922 (Box 10)
      - 1926-1932 (Box 10)
      - 1932-1936 (Box 10)
  - Reports
    - Deputations Reports, 1928-1935 (Box 10)
    - Questions and Answers about Yale Hope Mission, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Summer Interns' Reports, 1980 (Box 10)
- Records, circa 1965-1992; Accession 1997-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2027
  - American Automobile Association (AAA), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Asian American Students Association (AASA) Education Committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Asian American Students Association (ASSA) finances, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Accounting, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accounting programs, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Action, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adaptive Corporation, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Board, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Board, Advisory Committee, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Board, Executive Committee, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Board, Auditor's reports, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Board, Budgets, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Advisory Board, monthly report, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Board, Spring 1984 meeting (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Advisory Board minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Advisory Board nominees, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Advisory Board and budget, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - (Dwight Hall) Advisory Board information, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Board, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Aetna Life and Casualty Foundation, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Agendas/attendance, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Assistant General Secretary, Notes/Search, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Asian Community Services, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Alcohol/drug proposals, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
  - Alumni, Chicago, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Alumni, Los Angeles, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Alumni letters, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Alumni, New York, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Association of Japan, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Journalists, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Alumni letters, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Annual fund, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - (Dwight Hall) Annual Report, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Annual fund drive, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - (Dwight Hall) Annual Publication, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Articles about New Haven CISPES, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Articles and Literature by CISPES members, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Asian Americans at Yale, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Asian American, black resources, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Association of Yale Alumni, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Atlanta Child Murders, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Attorneys, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - AVA Speech, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Bank accounts, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bell Communications Research (Bellcore), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Benefits, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Benefits, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Benefits, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Berea College, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Birthday certificate, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Black-Jewish, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Block Watch, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - (Dwight Hall) Board of Directors, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - (Dwight Hall) Board meeting, April 29, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bonner Foundation, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bonner Foundation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Books to order, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Booth-Ferris Foundation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Boston Trid, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Boy Scouts, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Brokerage forms, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rhode Island (RI) Brown University, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Budget for 70's, Board of Trustees, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Budget for 70's, Budget (1970) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Budget (1974) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Budget, Investments, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Budgets and Audits (parts I and II), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
  - Budget, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - General budget, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Budget, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Budget and Activities, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Budget, quarterly report, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Budget, revised, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Budget, opening books, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Budget and Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Budget, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Building a Better Board, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - (Dwight Hall) Cabinet, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cabinet, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Cabinet and Board lists, past, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cabinet, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cabinet letters, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Cabinet Social Action Committee, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Cahoon reunion retirement planning, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Jean Cahoon project, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Herb Cahoon, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Yale calendar, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Campaign expenses, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Campaign plan, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Campaign, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - (Fay) Campbell plaque, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - (Olsen-Zapf) Campus Contact Service Award, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Campus Outreach Opportunity League, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Campus Outfitters, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Careers, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - (MN) Carleton College, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Carolyn Foundation, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Community Action by Students Together (CAST) meeting, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Summer, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cast, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Casual forms, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - (Fall) Campus and Community, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Centennial fund, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Centennial fund and Dwight Hall cabinet, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - (Dwight Hall history) Centennial Campaign, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chair caning, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chart of Accounts, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chaplain's office stuff, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - China Democracy Fund, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Christian Association, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dwight Hall Christmas Festival, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - City Wide Youth Coalition, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - CISPES I and II, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
  - Clark, F.A., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Clippings, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Clippings etc... pertaining to Dwight Hall, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Clippings in Japanese, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - (The) Commission on National and Community Service (CNCS), summer, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Coffin/soirée, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - (Doctor) Coles, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - College volunteers, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - College Volunteer Mailing Administration List 9, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - College and Universities in Connecticut, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Columbus House, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Columbus House Shelter Board Survey, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Columbus House, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Columbus House fundraising, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Comic book, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Commission on National and Community Service, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Communication with Advisory Board, All on Board, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Communications folder, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - (Henry) Community Organizations, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Community Organizations, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Community service, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Community service article, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Community Service Projects in New Haven, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 47-49)
  - Community service, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - (Connecticut) Community service flyers, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Commission on National Service and Community Service, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Computer, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Computer time, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Computer research, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Conference announcements, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, student run, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Conference, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Conference on East Timor, February 27, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Conferences and seminars, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Conference, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Connecticut Student Service Conference, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Consulting Group invoice, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Contracts, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - (Dwight Hall) Contacts in Japan, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Contributing correspondence, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Campus Outreach Opportunity League (COOL), newsletter, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Campus Outreach Opportunity League (COOL), resource book, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Campus Outreach Opportunity League (COOL), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Cooperative Consumers of New Haven, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Connecticut Higher Education Service Awards, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Contributors, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Corporate Volunteerism, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence; Morris, Cathy, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence; Meisel, Wayne, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondences, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Costs, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cross cultural information, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Current projects, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Corporate resolution, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 30)